

Yared Tolosa

Phone: 0974541532

Address: South Omo, Jinka

Email: yaredbirhanu20@gmail.com

Quick learner with academic abilities and technical knowledge to succeed in different roles. Ready to expand horizons with additional knowledge and abilities gained from training and experience. Always ready to help others and use abilities to support team goals.

EXPERIENCE

Bruh Tesfa Academy Football club

November 2019 - May 2021

Player

- · Adhered to club policies and regulations.
- Attended club activities, including meetings, training sessions and competitive games.
- Forged strong working relationships with players and club members.

Sewnet Charity Club

September 2020 - June 2022

Volunteer

- Recruited new volunteers to meet organisational needs and helped coordinate schedules, training and volunteer activities.
- Attended in-person and online training to learn about volunteer roles, safety requirements and organisational goals.
- Maintained excellent professional relationships by going extra mile to complete tasks voluntarily.

Ethio Genuine Consultancy

December 2022 - Present

Ambassador of the company

- Increased brand awareness with focussed social media marketing strategies.
- Communicated daily with team to recap campaign performance and make recommendations for next steps.
- Collaborated with design team to produce marketing and promotional literature.

EDUCATION

Bruh Tesfa Academy

High School Diploma

September 2017 - June 2022

- Member of student Union
- Best performance student Academic Achievement Award

SKILLS

- Event coordination
- Creative problem-solving
- Communication skills
- Leadership skills
- Creativit

LANGUAGES

Amharic (Native), English (Fluent)